Watch HD Anime and Movies: WWW.IFLIXASIA.COM
"Disturb not the harmony
of Fire, Ice or Lightning...
...lest these Titans wreak destruction...
...upon the world in which they clash.
Though the water's Great Guardian
shall arise to quell the fighting...
...alone its song will fail.
Thus the Earth shall turn to ash.
O Chosen One...
...into thine hands,
bring together all three.
Their treasures combined...
...tame the Beast of the Sea."
Now it begins.
Analysis indicates
that the Titan of Fire...
...referred to
in the ancient inscription...
...is the legendary Pokemon
Moltres...
...believed to have originated in
a remote region of the Orange Islands.
The Titan of Lightning
is the Pokemon Zapdos...
...and Articuno is the Titan of Ice.
Historical documents confirm...
...that the three legendary
Pokemon are unique species...
...found only in the vicinity
of Shamouti Island.
Moltres, Zapdos and Articuno.
Any one of them would be
a priceless addition to my collection.
But together...
...they are the three keys
that unlock the ultimate treasure.
Pokemon matching subject parameters...
...Moltres, Articuno, Zapdos detected.
Then let's get started.
Which one is nearest?
- The Fire Pokemon, Moltres.
- Good.
Now the chase is on.
Well, I've taken the first piece
without much difficulty.
It's like a simple game of chess.
Next I'll capture Zapdos,
and Articuno soon after.
And that will flush out the king.
And then, that's when the game
is going to get interesting.
"Bring together all three.
Their treasures combined tame
the Beast of the Sea.
Lugia."
Another perfect day in paradise.
The weather, warm.
The breezes, balmy.
The water, calm and crystal clear.
Even Pokemon trainers deserve
a break on a day like today.
As our heroes sail
through the Orange Islands...
...Ash Ketchum dreams
of his next big adventure.
Little does he know
it will be his greatest.
- Nice day!
- It's beautiful, right, Togepi?
Ash, think we have time to give
the Pokemon a little fresh air?
Sure, Tracey.
It'll take us an hour to get to the
next island. There's plenty of time.
Well, what are we waiting for?
We're way off course.
That's Shamouti.
We're right in the middle
of the Orange Islands.
- An island!
- In a storm!
I've seen this movie.
Do we have carp insurance?
- We're about to be...
- Fillet of fish?
Mime, mime, mime, mime.
Mime, mime...
Good morning, Delia.
- You certainly do have a green thumb.
- Thanks, professor.
But I've been getting a lot of help
lately. The weather's been beautiful!
Well, this is the time of year
when the sun shines every day.
Mime?
- Say, that was awfully strange.
- And it passed by so quickly.
Oh, my, it looks like snow!
Huh?
It is snow!
But this is summer.
How can it snow?
I don't know.
Mime!
What is it, Mimey?
- Mr. Mime is very upset.
- Yes, and so are the other Pokemon.
Pokemon are more in tune
with nature than we are.
When something's wrong,
they can sense it.
And I'm afraid something somewhere
is going terribly wrong.
We sure are lucky.
If we hadn't found this place,
we'd be in real trouble.
I think we still might be.
Maren, how are you?
It's been a while.
Carol, I can't believe it.
It's great to see you!
What are you doing back
on Shamouti Island?
We were in that storm and floated in.
It looks like we got here
at the perfect time.
You're right. The annual
Legend Festival starts today.
This is my favorite island holiday!
Are you the star of the show again?
No, I'm too old
to be the Festival Maiden anymore.
My little sister is taking over
for me. I wonder where she...
I'm right here!
The only one
not wearing some stupid costume.
You'd think you'd have outgrown
this dorky ritual.
It's our tradition.
You should be honored to take part.
Don't worry,
I'll play my role in the big legend.
- I've seen you do it a zillion times.
- Just be there!
Unfortunately, that's my little
sister. Her name is Melody.
But don't get fooled,
she's not always this adorable.
- Who's this?
- Oh, sorry.
This is Ash Ketchum.
He's a Pokemon trainer.
Pokemon trainer?
The ancient legend
foretells your arrival.
And only with you can
the Guardian of the Waters...
...vanquish the great Titans
of Fire, Ice and Lightning!
In your hands, O Chosen One...
...rests the world and its fate.
It does?
Don't let it worry you, kid. It's
just for the tourists! Blasted beak.
So you're a Pokemon trainer, huh?
I guess he'll do.
Here's your traditional welcome kiss.
- Are you his little sister?
- I am not!
Well, then I guess
you must be his girlfriend.
- Gross!
- Oh, I don't think so.
I'll be glad to play for him at the
Legend Banquet. Starts around eight.
Oh, and Misty...
...try not to get jealous.
We have found our Chosen One!
Deep-fried Festival cakes!
Get them while they're hot!
And she says,
"No, but I have krabbys."
That's ridiculous.
Me, Ash's girlfriend.
It's totally ridiculous.
I can't wait to see what my part
in the Legend Ceremony is going to be.
Ash, that's her!
The girl we met on the beach.
- Melody.
- Melody?
She's a big showoff.
Hear ye all!
"From the trio of islands
Ancient spheres shall you take
For between life and death
All the difference you'll make
O Chosen One, you must climb
To the shrine to right what is wrong
And the world will be healed
By the Guardian's song"
- What do I do?
- I just told you, Ash.
I heard all that stuff,
but what do I have to do?
It won't be very hard, Ash,
not for you.
Besides, almost all the Chosen Ones
come back alive.
Melody!
All you have to do is get glass balls
from three islands.
One from Fire Island, one from Ice
Island and one from Lightning Island.
And you bring them to the shrine
back here. And then...
...I celebrate by playing this song.
Then it's over, O Chosen One.
Do I get to wear a cool costume?
Sorry, but it's just come-as-you-are.
Besides, you look perfect to me.
The handsomest Chosen One in years.
Okay, get me a boat and I'm ready!
There's no hurry.
You have all day tomorrow.
Tonight's just for the party.
Stay, have some fun.
Some things are more important
than fun. I'm Ash, the Chosen One!
This is serious.
I got to be responsible.
That's a switch.
You know what?
I like your attitude.
- We can take my boat, Ash.
- Then let's go! You coming, Misty?
No, thanks! If you want somebody
to do whatever you want...
...you should find yourself
a girlfriend.
Pikachu!
Pikachu?
Hey, give me back my hat!
- Our ship is ruined!
- I'm sick over it.
I'm seasick over it.
- Wasn't that...
- The twerp?
And Pikachu too.
"Disturb not the harmony...
...of Fire, Ice and Lightning."
What a mess.
I hope the Legend Ceremony
doesn't include...
...a funeral!
This storm's bad. What if those two
can't make it to the island?
- Carol, I have to take your boat.
- But Melody, what can you do?
They're caught in the storm
because of our stupid ritual.
And I'm the one
who picked Ash for it.
I just hope they're all right.
- What are you coming for?
- To find Ash.
And don't start saying that I
secretly like him, because I don't!
You sure are sensitive about
someone who's not your boyfriend.
He's not my boyfriend! He's a boy and
a friend, but he's not a boyfriend!
You talking about me?
Togepi!
What we won't do...
...for Pikachu!
"Disturb not the harmony
of Fire, Ice and Lightning."
It seems there's been a shift...
...in the balance of power.
Pokemon Zapdos detected.
Experts believe that weather
disasters all over the globe...
...are due to a powerful
and unknown phenomenon...
...from deep beneath
the surface of the ocean.
This is a simulation
of the underwater river...
...snaking its way around the planet,
disrupting ocean currents...
...weather patterns and
the entire global climate.
I wonder if this is what's been
upsetting all the Pokemon.
The problem is centered at the north
central region of the Orange Islands.
The Orange Islands?
But that's where Ash
and his friends are right now.
Ooh, someone's calling.
- Professor, we're having problems.
- What is it, Professor Ivy?
The Pokemon here
are behaving very strangely.
- It looks like the storm's over.
- But the sea's getting rougher.
- The rudder!
- Pikachu!
- Well, at least we made it, but...
- Pika.
Pikachu, where are you going?
We shouldn't split up.
The storm might come again!
Pikachu's been acting really weird!
I gotta find out why!
Huh?
Okay.
Hold on, guys!
- Cool move.
- Been around boats all my life.
- You don't have to be scared.
- I never get scared out in the ocean.
I come from a Water Pokemon gym.
Hey. Are you guys okay?
Yeah, we're fine, but I think
the boat's in pretty bad shape.
Where's Ash?
Up there.
We're slipping!
It flies?
If you know how.
- Awesome!
- Hang on!
Let's find Ash.
Yeah, and if he needs any help,
his girlfriend's here.
But I'm not...
Like you said, you're a girl
and you're his friend.
Isn't that right?
Poor Moltres, you seem so miserable.
But they say misery loves company.
Zapdos approaching Fire Island.
Pikachu!
- Hey, look!
- There they are!
- I can't believe our luck.
- Yeah.
- Pikachu!
- We'll get you!
Oh!
Pika, Pika, Pikachu.
The ancient sphere.
- Guess who, Pikachu?
- Pika?
Huh? Was that...?
Prepare for more trouble
than you've ever seen.
Make it double,
we're on the big screen.
I'll have to catch this on video.
I'm in a hurry!
And the weather looks bad.
It has been bad.
Isn't that always our luck?
But our luck's changed
and our ship's finally come in.
I hope you're happy, Mr. Hero!
If you'd have stayed at the party
like I told you to...
...we wouldn't be stranded here.
- Welcome to my world.
I have to deal with his stubborn
attitude every single day.
You'll get used to it
when the two of you get married.
- Take that back!
- Listen to me, kid.
Getting involved with the opposite sex
is only asking for trouble.
Yes, and that's the kind of trouble
I stay out of.
You don't need the opposite sex
because you got each other.
- What does that mean?
- Not funny!
- Pikachu, it's Zapdos.
- Pika.
Pikachu, no!
Are you okay?
Pikachu's pretty tough, but Zapdos
isn't even feeling its attacks.
Those aren't attacks, Jessie...
...Pikachu's trying to talk to Zapdos.
- Pika!
It's saying, "What're you doing
on Fire Island, Zapdos?
- And where's Moltres?"
- Good questions.
- Translation?
- What's it saying?
It's saying,
"Moltres used to rule here.
But now that Moltres is gone,
Lightning shall rule over Fire...
...and I claim this island as my own
from this day forward!"
I guess Moltres flew the coop.
Absorbing Zapdos ' electrical energy.
Drained of its power...
...Zapdos will be too weak
to resist capture.
Once I've captured Articuno...
...the real prize will appear.
Code Blue Three.
When capturing Zapdos,
we collected something more.
More?
Zapdos...
...and Moltres.
Hey, what's this?
"Disturb not the harmony
of Fire, Ice or Lightning...
...lest these Titans wreak destruction
upon the world in which they clash."
This certainly is a pleasure,
though an unexpected one.
What do you think,
Moltres, the Bird of Fire...
...and Zapdos, the Bird of Lightning?
Of course, without Articuno,
it's not a complete set...
That's disgusting!
The way you talk, Pokemon are just
things to collect, like stamps!
What kind of trainer are you?
I'm afraid I'm not a trainer,
young lady.
I am merely a collector.
I began my collection
with a Mew card and...
...now I have all this.
Legendary Pokemon
have always been my passion.
And soon, my collection
itself will be legendary.
Sensors indicate Articuno
is changing course.
And now you'll have to excuse me.
The Legend. Could it be?
Here's a map of Shamouti Island,
the epicenter of the unprecedented...
...worldwide weather disasters.
Though not yet known why, thousands
of Pokemon are on their way...
...toward the island.
Water Pokemon are coming by sea...
...flying Pokemon are coming by air...
...and those on land are massing
together nearest the islands.
With me now are Professor Oak
and Professor Ivy to help...
...explain this phenomenon.
Near Shamouti lie the islands
of Fire, Ice and Lightning...
...home to the legendary birds
Moltres, Articuno and Zapdos.
I fear that they are somehow involved.
Ancient writings from many cultures
name this area...
...the islands of Fire and Ice,
as the cradle of the ocean.
The source of all the waters
of the world.
This has been disputed by scientists
for centuries.
But it makes poetic sense...
...when you consider what forms
when combining fire and ice.
What about the island of Lightning,
Professor?
Imagine an imbalance of power occurs
between Lightning, Ice and Fire.
Here's potentially
how the underwater current has formed:
If the balance between the powers
of Zapdos, Articuno and Moltres...
...were somehow disrupted,
a powerful underwater current...
...this Beast of the Sea...
...could emerge from this region and
ultimately flood the entire planet.
The Pokemon could be gathering because
they feel a sense of impending doom.
Pokemon are acutely in tune
with the balance of nature.
The urge to correct this imbalance
is causing them to gather...
...to try to save the planet, though
they may be unable to do anything.
And who are you?
My son is traveling
in the Orange Islands.
If things get as bad as Professor Oak
says, I may never see my boy again.
And Ash is the whole world to me.
I could use pants.
Melody.
This sure beats an in-flight movie.
"Disturb not the harmony
of Fire, Ice or Lightning...
...lest these Titans wreak destruction
upon the world in which they clash."
What if the legend is coming true?
If it is true, all intelligent life
will be destroyed.
- That's right.
- And I'll be...
You will be fine.
- We have to do something.
- Let's set Zapdos and Moltres free!
Yeah. But how?
Time to turn up the heat.
Pikachu!
I choose you, Charizard!
Fire and electricity aren't enough.
We can't just give up!
We must keep trying!
If things are going to get ugly,
we might as well try Weezing!
Right! Go!
Weezing!
Come on, you big palooka,
get up and fight!
Let's try Arbok!
Arbok, Arbok!
Now, Arbok, use poison sting!
Squirtle, Bulbasaur, I choose you!
- Squirtle!
- Bulbasaur!
Mayday, Mayday. Prepare for crash-
landing on Lightning Island.
Look out!
- I'd hate to get burned.
- I'd hate to get zapped.
I'd hate to get hit
by their droppings!
What's that sound?
Quick, we may need this!
Come on, hurry!
Take the treasure and put it there.
You can talk?
Pika, Pika.
Oh, right.
Fire Island.
Lightning Island.
So you're Ash.
You're one treasure short.
Yeah, I know,
but how'd you know my name?
Cut it out!
The Great Guardian, Lugia!
I can't believe it.
Lugia?
Pika.
That sound.
Finally, my prize.
It's magnificent.
The Beast of the Sea
will soon belong...
...to me.
"Though the Guardian of the Sea
shall quell the fighting...
...alone its song will fail,
thus the Earth shall turn to ash."
This looks bad.
What are they doing out
in this terrible weather?
- I'm worried about them.
- Save a little worry for us.
The fate of our planet is what
we should really be worried about.
The Pokemon know that
better than any of us.
There's only one hope.
Only the Chosen One
can bring together the treasures...
...to help the Great Guardian.
- The Legend says its song will fail.
And "Thus the Earth
shall turn to Ash."
How do we find the Chosen One if
we don't even know where to look?
It's right in the Legend.
"The Earth shall turn to Ash!"
Ash, it's talking about you.
I'm the Chosen One?
Pika, Pikachu!
Wait a minute.
Training Pokemons is tough enough.
But saving the world is way too hard.
I know it doesn't sound easy, Ash.
But you're the only one who
matches the Legend perfectly.
What do you say?
Right now I wish my mom had named me
Bob instead of Ash.
This whole thing is my fault.
I never should have dragged you
into this.
I guess I have to go along with that.
Don't blame yourself.
Ash always gets us into trouble.
- Yeah, but nothing like this.
- Huh?
Lugia. The sound it makes is just
like the song from the Legend.
The song...
The song has restored my strength.
But it alone...
...cannot bring harmony
to the three warring ones.
What do you mean?
When the treasures of Fire, Ice
and Lightning are aligned...
...my song shall harmonize
with their powers...
...and tame the beasts
both above and below the sea.
But this can come to pass only with
the help of the Chosen One.
What can I do that someone else can't?
Only in the hands of the true
Chosen One will the Ice sphere...
...glow like the others,
its power awakened.
I have to go there?
The choice is yours.
You must go only
where your heart leads.
Maybe I...
Pikachu!
I can?
Pika!
You think so too?
Okay.
I'll do whatever it takes
to get that third treasure.
But what if I mess up?
What if I...
- You can do it.
- We know you can.
Yeah, you're right, I can do it.
I'm the Chosen One.
Right now I feel more like
the Frozen One.
Maybe they got the wrong Ash.
Pika, Pika!
This is a lot better than walking,
Pikachu!
- We'll be there in no time, now.
- Pikachu!
Good luck, Ash.
- He's always the hero.
- We're always a zero.
We could be heroes too,
if we ever caught a break.
Huh?
I've got an idea!
We'll never get there now.
Who could that be?
If he thinks we're here for trouble...
...we're certainly going
to burst his bubble.
Instead of causing tribulation...
...we've undergone a transformation.
Though it's way outside
our usual range...
...we're going to do something
nice for a change.
- Jessie!
- James!
Up till now, Team Rocket's
been quite unscrupulous.
Being good guys for once
would be super-dupulous!
That's right!
What are they doing here?
You want to help?
- Of course.
- We don't want the world destroyed.
- Even if we survived...
- There'd be no one left to steal from!
We'd be out of work.
Come to think of it, when was
the last time we had a vacation?
We'll be on a permanent vacation
if we don't get to that island!
Let's do it!
- Evasive maneuvers!
- On the double!
- Up there!
- Pikachu!
Okay, you got the third treasure.
Let's get back to the island!
- Right.
- I almost forgot.
Pika! Pikachu!
Come on, let's go!
- The treasure?
- I got it!
Get on.
Pikachu!
Don't leave without us!
Hold on tight.
We're slowing Lugia down.
We're too heavy!
- Let's try Weight Watchers.
- Too late for that!
I heard it's never too late
if you really stick to the program!
If we don't let go,
they may not make it back!
Let's protect the world
from devastation!
Guess we gotta let go.
- Are you guys ready?
- Let's do it!
- What're you doing?
- Team Rocket's blasting off for good!
Team Rocket!
Think we did the right thing?
I know we did the right thing, Jessie.
And it feels great!
Well, this is it, then.
- Let's not say goodbye!
- Let's just say...
We're gonna die!
Lugia!
Why are all those Pokemon down there?
Because they feel they must be here
in case they are needed.
But what could they do to help?
They are not sure,
and that is why they are here.
- What do you mean?
- That just one Pokemon...
...could help the world would be worth
the journey for them any day.
But this day, the one that can make
all the difference is you.
Please hurry.
Let's hope the...
...Legend is true.
Hey!
Soon, Lugia, you will be mine and
my destiny will be fulfilled at last.
Pika-Pika!
I have failed.
Here, take this.
Legend or not,
Ash can't do this alone.
You'll have to play Lugia's song.
I'll go look for him.
Ash is never really alone
because he's got...
...me.
Ash!
Pikachu, just hang on!
Come on, Ash, breathe.
You've got to!
Please, Ash, please, you can't...
The sphere!
Ash.
Let me go! I gotta do this!
He made it!
Have you brought the final treasure,
Ash?
Here it is, Slowking.
You must be the one to place it.
The song.
As you can see
from these live pictures...
...severe weather that's caused havoc
around the globe has finally ended.
The Beast of the Sea has been tamed.
The fate of the world
could not have been in better hands.
Ash! Ash!
My lumbago!
It's my mom!
All right, start talking!
You are in big trouble, mister!
But Mrs. Ketchum,
Ash just helped save the whole world.
Oh, he did, did he?
Well, I could have lost
my whole world.
Every day I worry about you
and wonder if you're all right.
I know I can't stop you...
...from doing the things
you need to do.
I just can't help missing you
all the time.
You're a Pokemon trainer,
and that's just how it is.
But next time...
...could you try to save the world
just a little closer to home?
I guess I could give it a try.
And remember...
...every day...
...you're my hero.
Thanks, Mom.
Pikachu!
We've got to get back to Pallet Town
to tell the other Pokemon researchers!
Come on!
How it all began...
...and how I'll begin again.
Who'd believe it?
For once we were heroes.
- Too bad nobody saw us.
- Guess again.
What did you say?
Lots of people saw
what you did out there...
...and all of them are watching you
right now.
Then I guess the bad guys...
- Are finally...
- Good guys!
- So then we're not bad.
- That's good!
- What if the boss finds out?
- That's bad!
- We'll start our own team!
- That's good!
- But we got no money!
- That's bad!
- Then we'll just steal some!
- That's good!
Or is that bad?